{
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "א",
      "answers": ["alef", "aleph"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "בּ",
      "answers": ["bet", "beth"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ב",
      "answers": ["vet", "veth"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "גּ",
      "answers": ["gimel"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ג",
      "answers": ["ghimel", "gimel", "gimmel"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "דּ",
      "answers": ["daleth", "dalet"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ד",
      "answers": ["dhaleth", "daleth", "dalet"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ה",
      "answers": ["hey", "hay", "hai", "hei"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ו",
      "answers": ["vav", "waw"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ז",
      "answers": ["zayin"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ח",
      "answers": ["chet", "khet", "hat", "xat"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ט",
      "answers": ["tet"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "י",
      "answers": ["yudh", "yodh", "yud", "yod"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "כּ",
      "answers": ["kaf", "caf"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "כ",
      "answers": ["chaf", "khaf", "haf", "xaf"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ך",
      "answers": ["chaf sofit", "final chaf", "khaf sofit", "final khaf", "haf sofit", "final haf", "xaf sofit", "final xaf", "caf sofit", "final caf", "kaf sofit", "final kaf"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ל",
      "answers": ["lamed", "lamedh"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "מ",
      "answers": ["mem"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ם",
      "answers": ["mem sofit", "final mem"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "נ",
      "answers": ["nun"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ן",
      "answers": ["nun sofit", "final nun"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ס",
      "answers": ["samech", "samekh", "samex", "sameh"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ע",
      "answers": ["ayin"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "פּ",
      "answers": ["pay", "pei"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "פ",
      "answers": ["fay", "fei"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ף",
      "answers": ["fay sofit", "final fay", "fei sofit", "final fei", "pay sofit", "final pay", "pei sofit", "final pei"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "צ",
      "answers": ["tsadi", "tzadi", "tzadee", "tzadei"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ץ",
      "answers": [
        "tsadi sofit",
        "tzadi sofit",
        "tzadee sofit",
        "tzadei sofit",
        "final tsadi",
        "final tzadi",
        "final tzadee",
        "final tzadei"
      ]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ק",
      "answers": ["quf", "qof", "kuf", "kof", "qoof", "koof"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ר",
      "answers": ["resh", "reish"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "שׁ",
      "answers": ["shin"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "שׂ",
      "answers": ["sin"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "תּ",
      "answers": ["tav", "taw"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ת",
      "answers": ["thav", "thaw", "tav", "taw"]
    }
  ]
}
